# **Gerard Costa**

# Full Stack developer



Graduated in audiovisual systems engineering. I am passionate about the technological world and the web experiences that can be created to connect people. I enjoy programming, either with personal projects, or as a team using new technologies to continue growing in this exciting world of web programming.

# **Experience**

## Front End Developer | 2024

Freelance

- Basketball player scouting website.
- Front End technologies: NextJS, Typescript, Shadon, Tailwind.
- Other technologies: Git and Figma.

#### Full Stack Developer | 2023

Fundació Esplai

- Website centered on connecting users through "families" and hobbysharing events.
- Front End technologies: **HTML**, **CSS**, **Javascript**, **React**.
- Back End technologies: NodeJS, Express, MySQL, Postman.
- Project Team: Collaborated closely with a diverse team, employing agile methodologies and utilizing collaborative tools like Figma, Git and **Trello** to successfully deliver the project.

# Help Desk Technician | 2022 - 2023

Institut Català de Finances

Incident management, user service (in person and telematics), management and maintenance (computer equipment / servers / mobile devices).

# Amusement Park Operator | 2018 - 2021

Tibidabo

Teamwork, customer service and problem solving with clients.

# Education

#### Bootcamp fullstack developer javascript

Fundación esplai | 2024 (at the moment)

#### Bootcamp web developer

Fundación esplai | 2023 (336h)

#### Degree in engineering in audiovisual systems

Universitat pompeu fabra | 2018 - 2023

#### **Contact**



628 65 84 86



gerard.costa.curr@gmail.com



github.com/krutzzio



in /in/gerard-costa- gracia/



Barcelona, 08032

# Languages

SPANISH - NATIVE

CATALAN - NATIVE

ENGLISH - MID LEVEL (B2)

#### Soft skills

**TEAM WORK EFECTIVE COMUNICATION ADAPTABILITY** DISCIPLINED PROBLEMS SOLVER

#### Hard skills

HTML **NEXTIS** CSS **ASTRO VUEIS JAVASCRIPT REACT TAILWIND PYTHON GIT** 









## **Aditional Information**

- IMMEDIATE INCORPORATION
- FULL TIME